export const katakanaData = [
    { "id": 1, "question": "ア", "correctAnswer": "a" },
    { "id": 2, "question": "イ", "correctAnswer": "i" },
    { "id": 3, "question": "ウ", "correctAnswer": "u" },
    { "id": 4, "question": "エ", "correctAnswer": "e" },
    { "id": 5, "question": "オ", "correctAnswer": "o" },
    { "id": 6, "question": "カ", "correctAnswer": "ka" },
    { "id": 7, "question": "キ", "correctAnswer": "ki" },
    { "id": 8, "question": "ク", "correctAnswer": "ku" },
    { "id": 9, "question": "ケ", "correctAnswer": "ke" },
    { "id": 10, "question": "コ", "correctAnswer": "ko" },
    { "id": 11, "question": "サ", "correctAnswer": "sa" },
    { "id": 12, "question": "シ", "correctAnswer": "shi" },
    { "id": 13, "question": "ス", "correctAnswer": "su" },
    { "id": 14, "question": "セ", "correctAnswer": "se" },
    { "id": 15, "question": "ソ", "correctAnswer": "so" },
    { "id": 16, "question": "タ", "correctAnswer": "ta" },
    { "id": 17, "question": "チ", "correctAnswer": "chi" },
    { "id": 18, "question": "ツ", "correctAnswer": "tsu" },
    { "id": 19, "question": "テ", "correctAnswer": "te" },
    { "id": 20, "question": "ト", "correctAnswer": "to" },
    { "id": 21, "question": "ナ", "correctAnswer": "na" },
    { "id": 22, "question": "ニ", "correctAnswer": "ni" },
    { "id": 23, "question": "ヌ", "correctAnswer": "nu" },
    { "id": 24, "question": "ネ", "correctAnswer": "ne" },
    { "id": 25, "question": "ノ", "correctAnswer": "no" },
    { "id": 26, "question": "ハ", "correctAnswer": "ha" },
    { "id": 27, "question": "ヒ", "correctAnswer": "hi" },
    { "id": 28, "question": "フ", "correctAnswer": "fu" },
    { "id": 29, "question": "ヘ", "correctAnswer": "he" },
    { "id": 30, "question": "ホ", "correctAnswer": "ho" },
    { "id": 31, "question": "マ", "correctAnswer": "ma" },
    { "id": 32, "question": "ミ", "correctAnswer": "mi" },
    { "id": 33, "question": "ム", "correctAnswer": "mu" },
    { "id": 34, "question": "メ", "correctAnswer": "me" },
    { "id": 35, "question": "モ", "correctAnswer": "mo" },
    { "id": 36, "question": "ヤ", "correctAnswer": "ya" },
    { "id": 37, "question": "ユ", "correctAnswer": "yu" },
    { "id": 38, "question": "ヨ", "correctAnswer": "yo" },
    { "id": 39, "question": "ラ", "correctAnswer": "ra" },
    { "id": 40, "question": "リ", "correctAnswer": "ri" },
    { "id": 41, "question": "ル", "correctAnswer": "ru" },
    { "id": 42, "question": "レ", "correctAnswer": "re" },
    { "id": 43, "question": "ロ", "correctAnswer": "ro" },
    { "id": 44, "question": "ワ", "correctAnswer": "wa" },
    { "id": 45, "question": "ヲ", "correctAnswer": "wo" },
    { "id": 46, "question": "ン", "correctAnswer": "n" }
  ];
  